Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Here you go.
Beautiful.
Now,
this won't hurt a bit.
I can't breathe.
I'm sorry, I can't...
I just...
I'm sorry.
I can't, I can't do this.
I can't.
I'm sorry doctor.
Well, I guess I got time
for a round of golf now.
Alexa.
Are you okay?
A lot of our patients get
nervous the first time.
It's perfectly normal.
You know, I, um,
I'm just not ready.
That's okay.
When you are ready,
give us a call.
I'm happy to reschedule
you anytime.
- Okay.
- I'll think about it.
Thank you.
- Bye.
Hey babe.
Alexa here.
I just wanted to come on
and tell you guys that I know
there's a lot of stigma online
about plastic surgery
and the truth is honestly,
everyone has the right to look
and feel their best.
And I decided that
I am going to get
a procedure done,
um, with Dr. Bradford.
And if you're willing to face
your fears...
Since the
beginning, I see this girl.
I'm like, ah, you know,
I can't even find the right
words for it.
You know, she's eh.
Every time I see her,
I'm argh!
You're right.
Of course, I'm right.
I'm French.
French are always right.
Everything that is French
is right.
French fries, French toast,
French kiss.
So now you're going to forget
about this girl.
You are gonna go.
You and I in Paris
and I'm going to introduce you
to my whole family.
And I'm talking about family,
I'm not talking about
my grandmother.
Even if she's hot.
I'm talking about girls,
French girls, man.
Their fucking hot like French
toast and French fries.
Way better than her.
She's disgus...
Hey Alexa.
See you.
Paris.
You're drinking.
Gosh, Matt, it's 9:00 AM.
Why do you do this to yourself?
Where were you?
The doctors I told you.
Why are you back so soon?
Cause I can't go through
with it.
Can't go through with what?
The procedure, Matt.
I don't want to talk about it.
Sure you weren't with Trey?
Are you serious?
Yeah.
I faked a doctor's appointment
so that I can go
sleep with Trey.
Don't play dumb.
I saw the texts.
You're sweeping through
my phone.
I have to sweep through
your phone.
Saw the way your face lit up all
surreptitious last night,
smiling as he was texting you.
Oh my God.
You're so insecure
He's our friend, Matt.
I should be able to text our
friends without your approval.
Just cut the shit, Lex.
I know you're hiding something
and I don't like it.
I'm not hiding anything.
Is that him?
No it's my mom.
Hello?
Hi mom.
What?
Oh no, not again.
Okay.
No, I will.
Alright, I love you.
Bye.
Everything okay?
No, it's Becca.
She went away
from the rehab clinic again.
I have to go find her.
Alright.
Alright, wait, I'll go with you.
Let me change.
Okay.
Becca.
Alexi?
What are you doing here?
Mom called, fucking narc.
Becca, why'd you run away?
Some for me.
No one said it would be easy,
Becca.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know, I'll figure out
like I always do.
Yeah, like you always do
is how you ended up there
in the first place.
I'll be fine by myself.
What was your plan then?
Huh?
Selling your body on the streets
for drug money.
End up homeless.
Is that your plan.
Fuck you, Lexi.
What do you know about it?
Everything's always been handed
to you on a silver platter.
Why don't you just go back to
your NFL boyfriend
or your 15 million followers?
That's what this is about.
I was assaulted.
Did you tell someone?
Yeah, of course I told somebody,
but it didn't matter.
They just thought that I was
making it up
so I could get out.
I'm so sorry, Becca.
I'm sorry.
Morning, baby.
I have morning breath.
Baby, you know I don't care
about morning breath.
- Come here.
- No, Carl.
Let's get some love.
Okay.
- Ooh.
- What?
Hey Stop.
What?
You're okay.
- No.
- Come here, girl.
Hey.
Yo Kenny.
Door.
Crap.
Baby, you gotta go.
I forgot that Carl was having
people over.
But you said, I could meet
Trinity.
I know, next time, okay?
Well, that's what you said
last time too.
The stairs are at the back.
Are you serious?
Fuck you!
Bye babe.
Coming.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Look's good, dude.
What took you so long?
You know I'm just kicking
around here?
- I can see that, where Carl?
- He's upstairs.
He'll be down in a sec.
- Hey Alex.
- Hi Kenny.
Oh, hi.
Sorry.
Kenny, this one is my sister,
Becca.
Becca, Kenny.
Becca?
That's a pretty name.
Let me know if you need
anything.
I pretty much run this place.
Do you like surfing?
I got bit by a shark
a few years ago.
Wanna see the scar?
Wow.
Kenny 45 seconds in,
you're already talking about
the shark bite.
She's off limits, bro.
Hey, she's fine.
You're the one that said
watch out for Kenny.
She what?
- I'm done.
- Fine.
You need to chill?
You are just bad energy.
Well,
I've seen nothing has changed.
Man, good to see you.
Bro, it is good to see you.
How's the leg?
Man, costing me millions.
Come on, man.
You still looking like the MVP
out there.
I've got something that'll
cheer you up.
Now come on.
Wait till I show you this.
Man, I just got this bottle
of scotch imported
from Scotland.
Wooh!
Didn't you get that bottle of?
Did I?
Boy, I'm telling you,
I knew you'd enjoy that.
Carl?
What do you wanna show us?
Oh,
well actually that's exactly
what I wanted to toast about.
So look, I want you guys to be
the first to hear
Trinity's new single.
It just finished.
So I just, I want to hear what
you guys think.
I really want to know
your thoughts.
Who's thirsty?
You, you look like you need
a drink.
Huh, I don't think so.
- Come on, let her loosen up.
- Yeah.
She's not 21.
Okay.
Party pooper.
Baby, I wanna play the new track
for them.
Can you grab my laptop
from upstairs
and bring it back down please?
Okay.
Yo, I'm telling you
this song is sick.
I'm smelling number one
with this one.
Seriously.
I mean, Trinity has been working
her ass off.
She's unbelievable.
Just I feel so blessed.
Hey Sis, you a Trinity Lee fan
or what?
No, it's not my scene.
Okay.
I love a challenge.
Hey, it's not here.
Bottom drawer in the closet.
I already cleaned
it and it was not there.
Yo Kenny,
where's my beats?
I don't know.
Come here, come here.
Listen to me, dog.
That hard drive is worth more
than your life.
Alright,
so I need to know where you went
and what you did after
you left the studio.
Nowhere I came home.
And you didn't go anywhere else?
No, I came straight home.
Wait, actually I stopped
and got gas,
but that's it.
Where else did you go?
Nowhere.
It's in the car.
Kenny, where is it?
Kenny?
This is where I always put it.
Argh.
I swear I put it in there.
Yo, you find it?
No.
Oh man.
Hey, you should try that,
find my iPhone,
find my laptop app,
whatever it's called.
Yeah.
Actually Becky used it once.
Didn't you Bec?
She got her phone back.
Yeah.
It's your phone?
Yes,
he that's took at school and I drove
to their house and wouldn't
leave until they gave it
back to me.
This it?
Yeah.
What the hell is it doing way
out here?
Where is that?
Dude, I've never seen this place
before in my life.
I've no idea what that is.
Yeah,
well you are going to go get it.
No matter what it takes, man,
I need you to bring that
back here.
The computer I can replace.
What's on it, I can't.
Disappointing, man.
Get outta here.
Leave my phone, dumbass.
That's really harsh.
He's always doing this.
He's such a fuck up.
Okay, but he's your friend
and he's loyal.
He seemed to forget that
and take that
for granted sometimes.
Like he's always there for you.
It's like having a child.
Okay.
What's so wrong with that?
Babe, come back?
Yo babe, I still haven't heard
back from Kenny.
We need to talk.
- May I help you?
- Yes.
Sorry.
Do you live here?
Oh yes.
This is my home.
I'm really sorry to bother you.
But my family has lived here
for generations.
My son will be home
any minute, now.
Oh, I do enjoy our little chats.
It's so chilly out here.
Come inside.
How are you feeling?
Caught off guard?
Ill prepared, incompetent.
I'm scared.
I'm not ready for this.
Carl, you're not alone.
And you're a good man.
You're not your father.
You'll be an amazing dad.
Any words from Kenny?
No, still nothing.
Now, I'm really starting to get
worried now.
Maybe he got caught up
with something.
Are you kidding me?
He always texts me back
immediately.
Oh, Dr. Bennet is always messing
around with his patients.
Who's Dr. Bennet?
Whores, all of them.
I just made a fresh batch
of brownies.
Have one?
Hey, I just came by to get
my friend's computer.
Have a seat young man.
Now, do you like chocolate?
Thank you.
Oh, excuse me.
Awfully quiet in here.
Young lady what's your name?
- Kiana?
- Kiana.
Hi.
Whore.
How can I help you?
Have a seat.
Teach me everything you know.
It is just a release that
I am looking for,
and it is not happening.
Release,
you talk about sexual orgasms?
Yeah.
That'd be good, huh?
Ma'am, I've...
Have a brownie.
Well it's a
problem and we have to fix it.
I insist.
Are you game?
Teach me everything you know.
Whore.
Why don't we get
a little bit more acquainted?
Make your way
around here and take a seat,
right over there.
You are game?
Very.
- Look, I just...
- Do you think she's beautiful?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
But Dr. Bennett's always going
for those trashy types.
I guess so, but listen.
Not my grandson Philip,
there's a beautiful boy.
Listen lady.
If I can just please-
Do not yell at me.
Let me tell you a little story.
Okay.
There was once a town.
And it was very wet.
It was loveless.
And he couldn't find a home.
You were the home.
Open the door.
So what do you want to do?
Wanna head out?
You're being such a baby.
- I'm being a baby?
- Yeah, you're being a baby.
I'm pissed cause you're always
giving me attitude.
Like I forced you to come here.
I wasn't complaining.
I was just asking if you
wanted to leave.
I wasn't forcing you
to do anything.
You've been so mopey
ever since you got cut.
Do not bring that into this.
But it's true.
You're third string
running back.
You got hurt.
Shit happens.
How long were you expecting it
to last anyway?
Well at least I had a talent.
And I pursued it.
I'm not a superficial whore
for Internet likes.
Wow.
Jesus.
You gotta be kidding me.
Jesus Christ.
You want to play with me?
No, I can't.
I'm just looking for my laptop.
I think you have it.
What the fuck?
You're fucking alive, okay.
Okay.
Um, alright, let's get you
out of here.
I'll be right back.
I'll get some help, okay?
Oh shit.
What do you want?
We should talk.
About what?
You made yourself pretty clear.
Listen, I'm not coming here
to start anything.
I'm just trying to apologize.
Well, you're doing a bang up
job of it.
You know what?
Forget it.
Forget I said anything.
Guys, look, Kenny's still
MIA,
so we're going to go look
for him.
Y'all wanna stay or go?
Na, we're coming with you.
All right, man.
Becca.
What are you doing?
You okay?
Yeah.
So, yeah we're getting closer.
Looks like we're coming up
on it right now.
Should be right here.
Shit, yeah, look,
there's my car.
Yes, I guess this is it.
I don't like this,
should we call the police?
For what?
I don't know, maybe he's in
some kind of trouble?
Why don't we just see
what's up first?
All right, we don't need to
jump to conclusions.
Okay, how about this?
How about one of us stays here
and the rest of us go together
and if we're not back
in ten minutes,
then the other person calls
the cops?
I'll stay.
All right, let's do this.
Okay, you sure.
Yeah.
Okay, ten minutes.
Lock the doors.
I'm not to a kid, Lex.
Okay.
Yo, open up.
Yo, Kenny, you in there?
Oh.
Oh, how nice of you kids
to stop by.
You're just in time for dinner.
Come in.
- Come in.
- Na, we're good out here.
Can you just go get our friend
and we'll be on our way?
You come to see Philip.
How nice.
Philip, your friend is here.
Who the fuck is Philip?
I'll take it from here, Grammy.
Go on Dr. Bennett's waiting.
Oh, oh, lovely to meet you.
What can I do for you folks?
Look, bro, um,
my computer is here,
and I sent my boy to
come get it,
but we haven't heard back
from him, so
Where is he?
Your computer?
I'm not sure I know what you're
talking about.
Come on, dude,
cut the bullshit, all right?
It went missing.
We tracked it here.
So unless you like dealing
with the cops,
I suggest you just run upstairs,
go get my laptop,
get my friend.
I don't want to get pissed off.
Your friend is upstairs
in the bathroom.
Why don't you come
and wait inside?
No, we're good right here.
Just go get what I asked for
and we'll be on our way.
I don't know how long
he's going to be,
and I really don't want to leave
you outside on the porch
in the cold.
Carl, it's cold
and I got to pee.
Sir, can we use your restroom.
Sure, it's right down the hall.
Thank you, okay.
I'll tell you what,
I was just about to open
a bottle of Scotch.
Why don't you come inside
and have some while you wait?
Oh, shit, man,
that's a 20 year
old bottle of Glenholme.
Where did you even get that?
Friends in high places.
Trinity, your song sucks.
Matt?
Lex?
You found me.
Who are you?
My name's Timothy.
How did you get back here?
I don't know.
How did you open the trunk?
Well, look, you better get going
home, kid.
Your parents probably
looking for you.
You have cuts.
Yeah, I cut myself.
We cut people too.
What?
We make
people beautiful.
Okay, well,
you should probably get going.
I think you are
right, beautiful.
Thanks.
Philips, thinks you're
beautiful too.
Who's Philip?
Right behind you.
Lovely.
We're ready to eat.
You know,
you came at a great time.
Grammy's lamb chops
are simply superb.
We really can't stay for dinner.
We just came to get our friend
and get the laptop.
Right, of course,
although the smell may make you
change your mind.
Now about that drink.
Please.
And for you gentlemen.
Oh, I'm sorry,
I forgot to introduce myself.
I'm Dr. Jean Cunningham.
What kind of doctor?
I beautify people.
Oh, you're a plastic surgeon?
Yes.
Where do you practice?
In town?
How is the Scotch?
Smooth.
I serve my guests only
the finest.
Look, doctor,
we really got to get going,
we just came to get our friend,
and this wasn't meant to be
an all night thing.
We really have to get going,
no offense.
Of course.
Babe, it's just a drink.
No, not at all.
I understand young people are
so busy these days.
Dinner's ready.
Oh.
Well, help yourselves.
Wow, Granmmy,
that looks delicious.
Please, everyone, have a seat.
Kenny's not in the bathroom,
is he?
I'm sure he'll be down shortly.
Go get our friend and the laptop
right fucking now,
or I'm going to go get
them myself.
I see that you're upset
and you're right.
You've waited long enough.
I'll go get your friend.
Thank you.
Don't just stand
there before it gets cold.
Eat.
Hmm.
I'm afraid I have some bad news.
You have to understand
that my son can be overzealous
sometimes.
He tries his best,
but he just didn't have the same
training, I did.
Where the fuck is Kenny, man?
Oh.
- Oh!
- Shit.
Fuck.
Fuck!
Kenny!
Phillip did his
best, unfortunately,
this sort of thing happens
sometimes
in the medical field, no matter
how careful you are.
You're not a doctor
you're a psychopath!
In any case,
I can assure you
your procedures will be
much more successful.
You're insane.
Insane?
I'm going to make
you all beautiful.
I'm gonna make you fucking dare.
Matt!
What did you do to him?
Took a little while,
but I think the alcohol has
finally kicked in.
You drugged us.
I knew it would take a while
for you to come around
to my way of thinking.
What do you want
from us?
I want what you want.
Don't you want to look like
the women in the movies?
In the magazines?
I teach beauty for a living.
Yes, but you're not a doctor.
And unfortunately,
because you didn't have anything to drink,
I'll have to force it to you.
No, stop it.
You got blood on my shoes,
you ungrateful piece of shit.
Stop.
That's enough.
Prep him for surgery.
Go get your brother.
It's time for dinner.
Shh.
It's okay, there.
You weren't kidding.
There's work to be done.
So what will it be?
Larger breasts?
Fuller lips?
Perhaps higher cheekbones.
Alright, let's get started.
Looks like you had started
without me.
Maybe I can teach you
to make a more
precise incision.
You'll have to forgive me,
darling.
I don't happen to have access
to anesthesia.
Now, this will hurt quite
a bit.
I'll work as quickly as I can.
First,
we have to get rid of those
pesky clothes.
Philip.
Will you play with me?
I can't do it.
I will go get some help.
No, no, no.
Are you hungry, young man?
I just made some brownies,
if you're still hungry.
Would you like a brownie?
You're supposed to be healing,
young man.
Those wounds are fresh.
Do you how fast you people
can be?
None of us hee really considers
ourselves runners.
So we decided to hold on to your
feet until we were finished.
Then we would have given them
back to you.
But that'll be difficult now
that you're out of the ice.
Guess we better get started
now then.
No!
When you get back,
we're going to play.
We hope you enjoyed
your stay here.
Oh.
Nobody needs to know.
Look at these people.
Their miserable,
we're helping them.
Help me.
I'm stressed, I'm stressed.
This is a stressful job.
Sleep with me.
I can't wait any longer.
It's been a year.
Doctor.
In 5, quickie now.
Oh.
Well, well.
Looks like we've got a bit
of a logjam here.
Sorry, darling.
He was first.
But you're welcome to wait
until we're finished.
Philip, bring her closer
so she can see.
You people don't understand
how lucky you are.
I turn beautification
into a work of art.
Shall we take a look?
Philip, now.
What do you think?
I just took what she did
and finished it
in a professional manner.
I gave her everything
she wanted.
Look at my son, Philip,
I helped him become
his best self.
He wanted a few changes.
And who was I to argue?
Now, son.
Your nose is broken.
But luckily, we can fix that.
I can offer you anything
from Barbra Streisand
to Cyrano de Bergerac
to Michael Jackson.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It must be very difficult
for you to see
with your eyes
swollen shut.
You know, that tub of ice
was to reduce the swelling.
But not to worry,
I can help with that.
You seem to be having trouble
breathing, son.
I think perhaps we need to
open your lips.
Now, about that nose.
Matt.
Hmm?
Matt, you good?
We have to get out of here.
Fuck.
I'm sorry.
Matt.
Yeah.
I was trying to plan your
birthday party
with Trey.
That's why we were texting.
Oh, god.
I would never betray you.
I'm Timothy.
Will you play with me?
Help me.
Help me please.
Could you get us out of here?
I lost both, too.
Okay, okay, Timothy.
What do you want to play?
You'll play handball?
I'm really good at handball.
Yeah, I like handball.
You like it too?
I love it.
Don't you wanna play?
Yeah.
Okay, I'll tell you what.
I'll tell you what, Timothy,
if you get us out of here,
I'll play handball with you.
I'm not supposed to.
I know, I know you're not
supposed to.
But if you do this
I'll be your best friend.
Will you be the girlfriend?
Of course.
Of course I will.
But you have to get us
out of here.
Okay.
Just you.
No, it has to be the both
of us.
No, just you.
Just go get help.
I can't leave you.
When are we gonna play?
When I get back,
we're going to play
for a long, long time.
Okay?
I promise.
I'll even let you go first.
Pinkie promise.
Thank you.
Thank you, I'll be back for you,
okay?
I promise.
Becca.
Becca, Becca.
Oh.
Another one for the furnace.
Oh well, can't win 'em all.
Go give the couple upstairs,
another dose, will ya?
Make sure they stay out
while I work on this one.
Please, please.
Hello.
Hello, please, somebody
open up.
Wait a sec.
You got a bun in the oven?
Well, isn't that interesting?
You look so innocent.
I didn't realize you were
so promiscuous.
Luckily.
I can fix that too.
What is it.
The girl is gone.
What?
What are you waiting for?
You dumb shit.
Go.
I'll get the girl.
You don't go anywhere.
Please.
You have to help me.
What's going on?
My friends are trapped,
they took our phones.
I need a phone.
Can I use your phone,
please?
I'm afraid I don't,
sweetheart.
I'm sorry.
Can you take me to the
police?
Are you serious?
Yes, I need your help.
Oh, my God.
Okay, get in.
Thank you.
We need to go.
Thank you,
thank you so much.
They killed my friend Kenny,
and then he drugged
and kidnapped us.
That's unbelievable.
Don't worry.
We are gonna get you some help.
We're almost there?
I'm Mersea,
by the way.
Nice to meet you, Mersea.
I'm so glad you came,
because if you hadn't come,
I don't know what I would do.
Nothing to worry about now.
Please, this is where everything
happened.
- I need to go...
- Shh, don't worry.
It's nothing to worry
about now.
No, this is where everything
happened
I need you to go another way...
Becca.
I don't want to die.
I'm not going to let you die.
- I got you.
- Oh.
It's cold outside.
Hi, Mom.
Oh, hello, dear.
How was your evening?
Same as always.
Bad drivers, drunk arguments
and domestic violence.
What is this world coming to?
That's nice, dear.
What's Dr. Bennett up to?
Well, Dr. Bennett
is such a wonderful man.
I'll do that.
Jessica.
So tell me, Jessica,
sweet Jessica,
what seems to be the problem?
I've been having a lot
of chest pain that really,
you know, right by my breast
in this area.
This could be a very serious
problem.
I can help you.
Are you comfortable disrobing
by any chance?
Dr. Bennett,
I thought you'd never ask.
I actually didn't even wear
a bra just for this reason.
Oh, well,
you are a dream patient.
This is a problem.
I think we have to take
a closer look.
It's too bad all the women
he interacts with
are dirtier than the alley cats.
Women these days have no morals.
Basement.
What?
Basement,
they're in the basement.
He's killing them.
Let's go.
Ow, ow, ow, ow,
ow, ow.
Watch your step.
Don't give up.
Hey, you can do it.
Trinity.
Cal, Calvin!
Calvin!
One second, one second.
I got you, I got you.
Behind you!
You people are more trouble
than you are worth.
Ah we got a fighter.
Oh, is that sweetheart?
Lex?
Yeah. Get a good look.
Get a good look
at my masterpiece.
- Matt.
- She's a goddess.
Lex?
Have you heard
of anesthetic awareness?
When the patient is immobilized
during surgery.
But he can still see
and feel everything around.
Now we just have to wait
for it to kick in.
Lex.
What?
You don't like it?
I knew it was a brilliant idea
when I realized she loves
cutting almost as much as I do.
Sick bastard.
Put a lid on it.
I granted her wishes.
A fight to
the very end.
I admire that.
You're a fucking dead man.
This has been in my family
for many generations,
hasn't been used
in maybe
hundred years.
How are you doing, sir?
Looks like it finally kicked in.
Wow.
You are quite the specimen.
Bet you're a big hit
with the ladies, huh?
Yeah.
Oh, look at those arms.
Wow.
No!
Come and see.
Come and see!
You bastard.
Shut up bitch!
No, no, my beautiful boy.
We can fix it.
It's okay, it's okay.
And as for you.
When I kill you,
there'll be nothing left to fix.
Well, that's for you.
Oh, I wanted to give you
a beautiful face.
Oh!
Go, go get her.
Okay, where are we?
We'll be there in a minute.
Just look for 6825.
6825?
Every single number
on the street starts at 47.
There's no way we're
in the right neighborhood.
I think we're supposed to take
one of the side streets
back there.
How is it you've been here
before?
Yeah, I've been here once,
like four years ago.
They're probably wondering
where the hell we are.
Yeah, they're wondering
where I'm at.
I never even told
them you were coming.
Are you serious?
Stop!
Oh, shit, you're hurt.
You're bleeding.
Is he dead?
No, but she's bleeding a lot.
Can you please call a hospital?
Okay got a hospital 18 minutes
from here.
Oh yeah, we can drive there.
Can you help-go open the door,
open the door.
Are you okay?
Look at her face.
Okay, it's
okay, settle down.
We're gonna go to the hospital.
No!
- You okay?
- No, no, no!
Can I help you?
Actually I saw the lights
and wondered if I can help you.
We're okay, thank you.
I'm just trying to be helpful.
Okay, thank you.
Oh my god.
We should go.
No!
You are coming home with me.
Yo, what are you doing?
Get away from her,
I'm going to film you right now.
Get these bodies in the car.
Can you play with me right now?
Yeah.
Let's play, Timothy.
Let's play.
Relax darling,
you're about to become
my masterpiece.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull